<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goldthorpe Scouts</title>
    <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Goldthorpe Scouts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Parents</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/parents/</guid>
      <description>Parents are really important to us at Goldthorpe Scouts and we love to hear from you about what we are doing well and even more importnaly what we can do better. Its important we have good communication between the leaders and parents to make sure you know exactly what is going on and feel as included in scouting as your young person.
To make sure we are keeping you up to date you will receive frequent sms messages and emails from the section leaders but alsways feel free to grab one of us at the end of a session if you have any questions or concerns at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our new site</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/posts/welcome-to-our-new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 12:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/posts/welcome-to-our-new-site/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our new look website
We have spent some time creating a new site with a much better layout and lots of much better content to help you find out about us.
We hope you like it.
The entire site has been created using free and open source software. The source code for the site is hosted here https://github.com/GoldthorpeScouts/goldthorpescouts
You can see all of our content and you could even contribute a new blog post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 03:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description>We would love to hear from you. If you have any questions please contact us using the form
You can always find us on Facebook or Twitter the links are at the bottom of every page.
We look forward to hearing from you!!!
If you need to send us a good old fashioned letter you can send it to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks for Contacting Us</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/contact_thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 13:38:38 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/contact_thanks/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for touching base with us. Someone from Goldthorpe Scouts will be in touch soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beavers</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/beavers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 21:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/beavers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;The best thing we did was swim in the rain. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t even sure we were allowed to, but it was brilliant! I mean we were wet anyway, so I guess it didn&amp;rsquo;t matter too much about the weather.&amp;rsquo;
 Activities Beavers are our youngest members, and generally meet for an hour per week. They enjoy all that scouting has to offer; being introduced to outdoor activities, having the opportunity to be creative, explore their local community and experience the excitment of a Beaver Scout Sleepover with their friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cubs</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/cubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 07:39:12 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/cubs/</guid>
      <description>The best part of Scouting is definitely the camps. I love every activity we do apart from swimming. They told us the pool was 24 degrees centigrade. Minus 24 more like!’
 Activities For Cubs, excitement and adventure are key. Their programme offers a huge variety of activities surrounding areas of fitness, global and beliefs; whilst allowing them to be creative and get involved in their local communities. Cubs are introduced to exciting outdoor skills and take part in adventurous activities, as well as camps and residential experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scouts</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/scouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 21:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/scouts/</guid>
      <description>Scouting has given me a fantastic opportunity to do lots of activities and things that people who are not in Scouts don’t get to do. It’s about having fun with good friends.
 Scouts aims to build and develop young people’s confidence, sense of adventure and outdoor skills, as well as encouraging them to explore their beliefs and attitudes and be creative. It offers them the independence to put these skills into practice at camps and even on international trips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaders</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 14:27:13 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/leaders/</guid>
      <description>All the Groups leaders are volunteers. They give their time for free. But they are trained volunteers - the Scout Association has a thorough training programme that all Leaders have to undertake.
All leaders have to undergo a full Disclosure Barring Service (DBS) criminal records check, supply personal references and be approved by an Adult Appointments Committee before their first appointment. Appointments are also subject to regular review and renewal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Goldthorpe Scout Group was one of the first 100 groups in the world to be established in 1908, originally as the 1st Don &amp;amp; Dearne (Goldthorpe), according to a Scout Association fact sheet, which you can access here: http://scouts.org.uk/f103775
In the 1970’s the council boundaries changed so that Goldthorpe came under Barnsley rather than Doncaster, and the Scout group became known as the 6th Barnsley (Goldthorpe) Scout Group and ran successfully until around the start of the new millennium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/join/</guid>
      <description>If you have a young person aged 6 to 14 you they can come along and join the adventure.
We just need some information about your young person to make sure which section they fit into and make sure we have all the right information to ensure they have a great time with us.
Please fill in our application form.
If you have any questions please dont hesitate to get in touch with us via our contact form</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/facebook/</guid>
      <description>  Goldthorpe Scouts </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2019 Camp - Silverwood</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/posts/may-2019-camp-silverwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/posts/may-2019-camp-silverwood/</guid>
      <description>On the 30th May 2019, Goldthorpe Scouts and Cubs are attending a Group Camp. Keep coming back for regular updates on what we get up to.
May 2019 Group Camp Program
Thursday:
Arrival Time From 4pm.
4pm – 7pm Pitching tents, unpacking their personal kit and other jobs related to building the camp.
8pm – 10.30pm Snacks and wide game.
10.30pm washed and bed.
Friday.
8am – 9.30am breakfast.
Tent Inspection!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Links</title>
      <link>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/useful-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.goldthorpescouts.org.uk/useful-links/</guid>
      <description>New members</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>